Eli Scruggs
was the handiest of all handymen.
是杂务工中的好手
You could ask any of his customers,
你可以问他的任何一位雇主
and they would tell you,
他们都会告诉你
There was nothing he couldn't fix.
他无所不修
Whether it was a broken vase...
无论是破花瓶...
a leaky pipe...
漏水的管道...
or a shaky banister,
还是摇晃的扶手
Eli always knew how to get the job done.
Eli总能得心应手
But sadly,
但可悲的是
the man who had fixed so many things
这个为紫藤巷居民
for the residents of Wisteria Lane
修好如此多东西的人
was now about
即将
to break their hearts.
让他们"心碎欲裂"
Eli Scruggs, get down from there!
Eli Scruggs 下来!
Mrs. Mccluskey.
Mccluskey太太
Just found this note in my mailbox.
我刚在邮箱里找到这个便条
Says you're retiring? What the hell?
写你要退休了? 搞什么鬼啊?
Yes, ma'am. It's true.
是的 太太 是真的
Now why would you want to do something stupid like that?
你为什么要做那样的蠢事?
My doc says I got a bum ticker,
我的医生说我心脏有问题
Have to take it easy from now on.
必须从现在起好好休息了
Well, once I'm done fixing Mrs. Mayer's shingle
我一修好Mayer太太的房顶
- I'm on a plane to Waikiki.
- 我就要飞去怀基基海滩了(夏威夷)
Well, this is very annoying.
这事真够烦人
Who's gonna fix my water heater when it breaks?
我的热水器坏掉时 找谁来修呢?
Oh, I met this young guy named Toby.
我认识个叫Toby的小伙子
Very bright, just turned 30. He'll take care of you.
人很聪明 刚刚30岁 让他来处理吧
Ah, damn it, Eli!
去你的 Eli!
I am not comfortable with strangers in my house.
我不喜欢让陌生人到家里来
- Took me ten years to trust you.
- 我花了10年才完全信任你
I know.
这我知道
Most of those guys leave tools and nails all over the place.
那些人总是到处丢工具和钉子
You never leave a mess.
你从不搞得一团糟
Thank you, ma'am.
谢谢夸奖 太太
Have you told everyone else you're leaving?
你跟大家都说了你要走的事了吗?
I left copies of that same note in everybody's mailbox.
我在每个人的邮箱里都留了那张一样的字条
Well, that's not right.
那可不太好
After all these years, people will want to say good-bye,
毕竟这么多年了 大家都会想跟你道个别
and... You know, maybe throw you a party or something.
可能... 比方说为你搞个聚会什么的
Oh, no. I prefer to go quietly, if you know what I mean.
不 我希望悄悄的走 希望你明白我的意思
I don't want a big fuss.
我不想搞得大惊小怪
Well, I'll miss you, Eli.
我会想你的 Eli
There will never be another one like you.
不会再有像你这样的人了
With that Eli Scruggs climbed his ladder
就这样 Eli Scruggs人生最后一次
for the very last time.
爬上了他的梯子
And once he had finished making his last repair,
刚修完最后一样东西
Eli Scruggs... quietly, with no fuss...
Eli Scruggs... 静悄悄的 没有大惊小怪的...
Had a heart attack and died.
心脏病突发 离世了
And most importantly...
最重要的是...
Without leaving a mess.
没有搞得一团糟
It took an hour for someone to finally notice
一小时之后 才有人发现
the body laying at the top Susan Mayer's roof.
躺在Susan Mayer房顶上的尸体
It was less than ten minutes later
不到十分钟后
that the neighbors began arriving,
邻居们陆续赶来
Each determined to get a look
他们都想看看
at the various paramedics and policemen
各种各样的护理人员和警察
who were all frantically trying to figure out
看他们迫切的想弄清楚
exactly how to bring the body down.
具体的死因
And it took two days for my friends to realize
我的朋友们花了两天才意识到
this tragedy had affected them...
这场悲剧也影响了她们...
We're ready! Come on.
我们都好了! 来吧
More than they were willing to admit.
尽管她们不愿意去承认
Hey, Gaby, did you remember to get change?
嘿 Gaby 你记得带零钱了吗?
'Cause when I cash in my chips, I don't want to hear you say,
因为我不想在把筹码兑换成钱的时候 听到你说
- "all I've got is $50s."
- "我只有50元的钞票"
Speaking of cashing in your chips,
说到把筹码换成钱
- anyone know when eli's funeral is?
- 有人知道Eli的葬礼是什么时候吗?
Oh, I think it's Saturday.
我想是星期六吧
I wonder how many people are gonna show up.
不知道有多少人会去参加
- Mrs. Mccluskey was saying he didn't have much family.
- Mccluskey太太说他没什么亲人
Poor Eli. We should make sure he's got flowers at his funeral.
可怜的Eli 我们得保证葬礼上有人送花啊
I'm in. How much are we talking?
算我一个 要花多少钱?
I don't know. What do you think, Gaby?
不知道 你觉得呢 Gaby?
Gaby?
Wow! Jimmy Choo!
哇! Jimmy Choo!
Oh, Carlos!
噢 Carlos!
These aren't even in the states yet.
这款还没在美国上市呢
What's the catch?
有什么目的?
What are you talking about?
什么意思?
You never buy me a present
除非我生气了 或者要生气
Unless I'm mad or about to be mad.
你是不会给我买礼物的
And I don't think I am, so why am I about to be?
我想我现在还不生气 那么我会因为什么而要生气?
- I have to go to Cleveland tomorrow.
- 我明天要去克利夫兰
Carlos!
They're begging me. The merger's going south.
- 他们在求我了 兼并活动要向南进行了
You just got home!
可你刚回家啊!
With shoes.
买了双鞋
Don't leave me here. I'm going out of my mind.
别把我丢在这儿 我都要疯了
Everyone is so boring and suburban.
人人都那么无聊 那么老土
And how many freaking honor students
一个这样的学校会有多少
can that school have?
怪异的好学生?
Can we please not argue in front of the handyman?
- 可不可以不要在杂务工面前吵架?
He has a name.
他有名字的
What's your name?
你叫什么?
Eli Scruggs.
Eli Scruggs
You hear that, Carlos?
你听到了吗 Carlos?
You've brought me to a place
你把我带到了一个
where people are named "ElI Scruggs."
人们叫做"Eli Scruggs"的地方
Fine. I'll give up my job...
好吧 我放弃工作...
And everything that comes with it.
以及工作带来的一切
Not the Jimmy Choos.
Jimmy Choos不算
They're the only friends I've got.
这是我唯一的朋友了
Thought so.
我想也是
I'm going to pack.
我去收拾行李
You know, it's none of my business...
你知道 这和我无关...
You're right. It's not.
没错 和你无关
But the ladies in this neighborhood
但社区里的女士们
- are actually pretty nice.
- 其实人都很好的
Yeah. They came by, brought muffins.
没错 她们来拜访过 还带了松饼过来
One of 'em wants her basket back.
其中有一位还想拿回篮子
That'd be Bree.
那一定是Bree
Anyhow, she and the other ladies, uh,
不管怎样 她和其他女士们
play poker every week.
每周都打牌
If you'd like, I could talk to 'em,
要是你愿意的话 我可以跟她们说说
see if they'll let you host a game.
看她们要不要让你主办一次
Hi. We're, um... The neighborhood.
你好 我们是... 邻居
Gabrielle invited us to play poker.
Gabrielle邀我们来玩牌
So... Is she in?
那... 她在家吗?
Mrs. Solis will be right down.
Solis太太马上下来
She likes to make an entrance.
她喜欢来个"登场亮相"
What does that mean, "an entrance"?
什么意思 "登场亮相"?
Hello there.
大家好
Welcome to my home.
欢迎来我家
Oh.
噢
That's what it means.
就是那个意思
So I said, "pumpkin"...
于是我说 "南瓜"...
That's what I call Jon Bon Jovi...
那是我给Jon Bon Jovi(著名歌手)起的外号...
I said, "pumpkin, even if I could steer a yacht,
我说 "南瓜 就算我会驾驶游艇
I'm certainly not about to do it in 5-inch heels."
我都不会穿5英寸的高跟鞋做这个的"
True story.
这是真的
Well, you've certainly had quite a glamorous life.
你的生活一定热闹非凡
Well, it was before my husband moved me here to east nowhere.
那是在我丈夫带我到东部这个不知名小镇之前
Seriously, I don't know how you girls do it.
说真的 我都不知道你们是怎么做到的
- Do what?
- 做什么?
Get out of bed in the morning.
早上起床啊
I've only lived here a month,
我才住了一个月
And I want to put a gun to my head.
就想在头上开一枪
You know what I mean?
你们明白我的意思么?
No, we don't.
- 不明白
There are no good nightclubs, no theater.
这里没有高级夜总会 也没有戏院
What do you do for a good time?
你们消遣时都做什么呢?
Well, we watch the kids play soccer.
我们看孩子们踢球
And the school drama department puts on some really great shows.
学校戏剧部也演几场不错的戏
And then there's church, of course.
当然还有教堂
Church.
教堂
Oh, you're serious.
噢 你没有开玩笑啊
Look, I know it's quiet here, but I think you'll find
听着 我知道这里是很安静 但是我觉得你会找到
There's a real charm to Fairview.
美景镇的魅力所在的
No, no, it's cute. It's cute. I get that.
不 这里很好 很不错 我知道的
It's just...
只是...
I was a top-tier fashion model,
我曾是个知名的时尚模特
And I guess I'm just gonna have to get used to the fact
我想我不得不去习惯
that the best part of my life is behind me.
我人生最辉煌的篇章已经翻过去这个事实
Good-bye doing vodka shots with Kate Moss,
告别与Kate Moss豪饮伏特加的时光
And hello
迎接
To sipping international coffee with you girls.
和你们共饮咖啡的日子
Full house.
三张一样加一对
Yes?
你好?
Hello. Is Mrs. Solis here?
你好 Solis太太在吗?
Oh, I got it. I got it. Go, go, go, go, go.
我来吧 我来 你快走 走吧
- Ma'am, here's the bill for fixing your sink.
- 太太 这是修理水池的账单
Okay. Thank you.
好的 谢谢
By the way...
顺便说一下...
You made quite an impression at the poker game.
打牌时你让大家印象深刻
- Really?
- 是吗?
Oh, yeah. The ladies can't stop talking about you.
是啊 女士们不停在讨论你
Aw. Well, I'm sure it was kind of exciting
我想对她们来说能和明星共处
for them to have a star in their midst.
一定是让人激动的事
Uh, let me think... Did they say "star"?
让我想想... 她们说了"明星"吗?
I heard, uh, "stuck-up," "obnoxious," "bitch."
我听到的是 "明星脾气" "讨厌" "贱人"
What?!
什么?!
You know, I went out on a limb to get you into that game,
你知道 我豁出去让你跟她们一起打牌
And then you go in there acting like
然后你表现得好像
- You're better than they are.
- 你比她们更优秀
Oh, my clothes said that, not me.
这是我的衣服说的 不是我
Well, did you ask them anything about their lives?
- 你有没有问问她们的生活?
Why would they want to talk about their lives?
她们为什么想谈论她们的生活?
Their lives are boring.
她们的生活那么无聊
Well, you know what's gonna be really boring?
你知道真正无聊的是什么吗?
You sitting here alone in this big house without any friends.
是你独坐在这个大房子里 没有朋友相伴
If I were you, I'd drop the attitude.
如果我是你 我就会放下架子
Learn to like your neighbors.
学会喜欢你的邻居们
Well, thanks for the advice.
多谢你的建议
You wanna add that to your bill?
要把这个加在你的账单里吗?
No. It's on the house.
不用 这是免费的
I brought muffins.
我来送松饼
That's so nice.
真不错
We were just...
我们只是在...
Playing poker, and I wasn't invited.
打牌 而我没被邀请
I know. I get it.
我知道 我明白的
I just wanted to tell you guys
我只是想告诉你们
I know I made a horrible first impression.
我给你们留下了很糟糕的第一印象
Now you know why models don't usually talk.
你们现在知道模特们为什么不怎么说话了吧
Because we say a lot of stupid, patronizing things
因为我们说的话都很愚蠢傲慢
that made people want to avoid us.
使得人们对我们避之不及
What I should've said was... My husband's never home.
我要说的本该是... 我老公从来不回家
I miss the city.
我想念大城市
I miss my life.
想念原来的生活
I'm lonely all the time...
我一直很寂寞...
And I could really use some friends.
我可以交些朋友
Anyway, here.
不管怎样 给
Now that's how you make an entrance.
你就这样"登场亮相"了啊
Gaby?
I'm sorry. What?
不好意思 怎么了?
We're getting a wreath for Eli's funeral. Are you in?
我们要给Eli的葬礼上送个花圈 要不要算你的?
Actually, why don't you let me pay for it?
就让我来付钱吧?
It can still be from all of us.
- 还可以算是我们一起送的
No, you don't have to do that.
你没有必要这么做啊
I sort of do.
有点必要的
Now let's play some poker.
我们来打牌吧
All right, time for my luck to change.
好吧 我该转运了
This hand is for Eli.
这一把是为了Eli
Hmm. Next hand is for Eli.
好吧 下一把是为了Eli
You know, if we're gonna have a get-together
知道吗 如果我们葬礼后要聚会的话
after the funeral, we should start thinking about food.
我们该开始讨论一下食物了
- And by "we" and "food," you mean Bree, right?
- "我们"和"食物" 你值得就是Bree吧?
I thought that was clear.
我想这不言而喻了
I'd be happy to. Any special requests?
我很乐意 有特殊要求吗?
How about we pick something from your cookbook?
要不从你的食谱里挑一些吧?
Great. Gaby, do you have your copy?
好啊 Gaby 你那本在吗?
I'll go get it.
我去拿
You use my cookbook to balance your table?
你用我的书来垫桌子?
Oh, it's only temporary.
只是暂时的
Juanita needed her coloring book back.
Juanita把她的图画书拿走了
All right.
好了
Watch out, ladies.
当心点 女士们
I'm sorry if the frittata is a bit dry.
抱歉煎蛋饼是不是有点焦了
Are you kidding? It's great.
开玩笑的吧? 很好吃啊
- You should give Lynette the recipe.
- 你该把菜谱给Lynette
Yes, 'cause that's what
没错 因为那就是
Women in their eighth month really crave... more stove time.
- 女人在怀孕第八个月时所渴望的 多烤点东西
Mine is so erratic.
我的菜谱不很确定
I'm not even sure what the real temperature is.
我甚至不确定温度到底是多少
Of course, if a certain doctor
当然 如果某个医生
Would loosen the purse strings...
- 愿意松一下钱包链子的话...
We're not getting a new stove.
我不会再买个新的烤炉的
If you would just take on a few more patients,
只要你多接待几个病人
- We could afford it.
- 我们就买的起了
Well, if I'm not supporting you adequately, my dear,
亲爱的 如果我没有充分支持你
- by all means, feel free to do something about it.
- 请尽一切办法做点什么吧
Such as?
比如说?
Well, you could maybe... I don't know, get a job?
也许你可以... 我也不知道 找个工作?
I have a job. I'm a homemaker.
我有工作啊 我是个家庭主妇
And a damn good one. So to make this,
这个真好吃 要做这个
- You... you just s-saut some ham and some onions...
- 你... 你弄了些火腿和洋葱...
It's not happening, Tom.
没事的 Tom
I just sometimes think
我有时候想
maybe you would appreciate the value of a dollar more
如果你在外工作
If you had to work outside the home.
也许你会更重视钱的价值
And I think you would appreciate my value more if, for once,
而我认为 如果你哪怕有一次自己做饭洗衣
You had to cook your own food and wash your own clothes.
也会更重视我的价值
- Lynette makes me sew my own buttons.
- Lynette让我自己缝扣子
I'll sew anything you want
要是你不再让我怀孕了
If you just stop getting me pregnant.
让我缝什么都可以
I want a new stove, Rex,
我想要个新炉灶了 Rex
And if I need to get a job to pay for it, so be it.
如果我需要找工作来支付炉灶的钱 我会的
If you're looking for a stove,
你要需要炉子的话
We've got one that's hardly ever been used.
我们倒是有一个几乎没用过的
I wish I could say the same for my uterus.
我也希望能对我的子宫说同样的话
Oh, yeah. I ruined the brunch.
哦 好吧 早午餐让我给毁了
Hey, how's it looking under there, Eli?
嘿 下面情况怎么样 Eli?
Is it gonna cost me an arm and a leg?
需要花我很多钱吧?
Nah. A few fingers, maybe.
不会 可能就一点点
Honey, my stomach's growling. When's dinner?
亲爱的 我肚子都叫了 什么时候吃晚饭啊?
Oh, we're having leftovers.
哦 我们有些剩饭剩菜
You can heat them up yourself if you want.
如果你愿意的话 可以自己热热
Since when do we have leftovers?
什么时候咱家开始吃剩饭剩菜了?
Since I started writing my own cookbook.
自从我开始写我自己的菜谱
Remember how you told me
还记得你怎么跟我说的吗
I should start making my own money?
我应该开始自己赚钱?
Well, I've been going through all my old recipes,
嗯 我浏览了一遍我所有的旧食谱
And I've got this great idea
然后我就有了这个伟大的想法
- For a real home-style American cookbook.
- 编撰一本美国家常菜食谱
You're not serious?
你不是当真的吧?
Why wouldn't I be?
为什么不呢?
- People are always complimenting me on my cooking.
- 人们都在赞美我的厨艺
You're great, but come on.
你是很棒 但是得了吧
Every bored housewife who pulls off a decent lasagna
每一个能做出像样的烤宽面条的无聊的家庭主妇
Thinks she can write a cookbook.
都认为她自己能写一本菜谱
You think I'm just like every other housewife?
你认为 我就跟其他的家庭主妇一样?
No. No, no, no. That's not what I’m saying. It's just that...
不 不 不 我不是那个意思 只是…
What do you really know about writing
你知道什么是写作吗?
I'll learn. And I want it to be more than just a cookbook.
我可以学呀 而且我想让这本书不只是一本菜谱
I want to talk about traditional values
我还想谈论传统的价值观
And give helpful hints about homemaking.
然后给一些持家的建议
Look, look, this is my fault.
听着 听着 这是我的错
You know, I... I was ribbing you the other day
你知道 我... 我前几天是嘲笑你说
About getting a job, but you took it seriously.
你真该找工作 但你却当真了
If you really want a new stove, I'll get you a stove.
如果你真想要个新炉灶 我会买给你的
Now can you stop this foolishness
现在你能停止这愚蠢的做法
And make me something to eat that isn't leftovers?
然后给我做一些不是剩饭菜的东西吃吗?
Mrs. Van de Kamp?
Van de Kamp太太?
I fixed your banister. Should be fine now.
我把你的楼梯栏杆修好了 现在应该好了
I'll just go. You can pay me whenever.
我要走了 你可以以后再付账
I know this is a rough time for you.
我知道你现在不好过
Thanks, Eli.
谢谢你 艾利
By the way,
顺便说一下
The service for Mr. V. was really nice.
V先生的葬礼真的很不错
You were there?
当时你在那儿?
I sat in the back of the church.
我就坐在教堂的后面
I wanted to say good-bye to Mr. V.
我想跟V先生道别
So, uh...
所以 呃...
Have you thought about what you're gonna do now?
你有现在的打算么?
You mean, with my life?
你是说 我的人生?
I don't know.
我也不知道
Mrs. V...
V太太...
I've been meaning to give this to you for a while now...
我一直想把这个给你的...
But I, uh,
但是我 呃
Could never find the right moment.
一直找不到合适的机会
I kept it for you, just in case you might need it someday.
这个我一直替你保留着 万一某天你会用到它
Hope you don't mind.
希望你不会介意
Oh, I gotta tell you. I made your Cajun meatloaf.
哦 告诉你哦 我照着你的菜谱做了法式夹肉面包
Whoo!
哇!
That may be my favorite meal ever.
那可能是我最喜欢的一顿饭
I can't believe you saved this.
真不敢相信 你竟然保留着
Ah.
啊
Of course, I'm not really in the mood
当然 我现在真的没有心情
To write a cookbook right now.
写菜谱
Well...
好吧...
Maybe one day you will be.
也许有一天你会的
Hey, Bree, I know what you can make for the wake...
嘿 Bree 我知道你能为守灵做什么吃的了...
That flaky-breaded-shrimp thing.
那个薄片虾仁儿面包
Thanks, but I know exactly what I'm gonna make.
谢谢 但是我知道我该做什么了
Dave，it was a nice trip. But I gotta tell you.
Dave 旅行很愉快 但是我得告诉你
I don't know why we spent all that money going to the Bahamas.
我不知道为什么我们要花那么多的钱去Bahamas
If we're not gonna leave the hotel room,
要是我们不出旅馆的话
Then why not just cover ourselves in suntan lotion
那何不涂上防晒油
And have sex here?
在这儿做爱呢?
You just got a message from Mrs. Mccluskey.
你有一条来自Mccluskey夫人的短信
Oh?
是么?
She said your handyman died.
她说你们的杂务工死了
Eli?
Oh, my god.
哦 天啊
He was working on Susan's roof
他当时正在修葺Susan的房顶
And dropped dead of a heart attack.
然后死于心脏病突发
Can you believe that?
你能相信么?
No, no, no. You are not going to the gym again.
不行 不行 不行 不许你再去那健身房了
You said we were gonna have afternoon sex.
你说过下午要和我做爱的
- We'll do it when I get back.
- 我回来了再做
You say that every time, Umberto,
你每次都这么说 Umberto
- And then you're too tired.
- 然后你又太累了
Maybe I wouldn't be if you weren't so clingy.
你要是不那么粘人 或许我就不会那么累
Clingy?
粘人?
We haven't had sex in two weeks.
我们有两个礼拜没做爱了
It's like I'm 15 again. What's wrong with us?
我好像又回到了15岁 我们之间是怎么了?
Not us. You.
不是我们 是你
Your libido is out of control.
你的性欲太强烈了
Umberto...
Look, you've got a drawerful of toys. Use 'em.
听着 你有一抽屉的成人用品 就用他们吧
Oh!
咳咳!
Ahem.
呃
Oh!
哦!
Oh! Eli! I... I forgot you were in there.
哦! Eli! 我... 我忘了你还在里面
Yeah. I'm done fixing your faucet.
是啊 我修好你的水龙头了
Actually, I was done ten minutes ago,
事实上 我10分钟前就弄好了
- But I was afraid to come out.
- 但是不方便出来
I'm sorry you heard all of that.
很抱歉你都听到了
The good news is, while I was in there,
好消息是 我在里面的时候
I re-grouted your tub... Free of charge.
顺便把你的浴盆也给弄好了... 免费哦
Wait a second.
等等
What do you think of my ass?
你觉得我的臀部怎么样?
Sorry?
什么?
My ass... on a scale from one to ten.
我的臀部... 从一到十评分
Well, I... I... I, uh...
呃 我... 我 呃...
Ticktock.
快点
Ten. It's a ten.
十分 是十分
And the boobs? Perky and firm?
那胸呢? 坚挺而又紧致?
You've named them?
你给她们取名字了?
Oh, come on, Eli.
哦 得了吧 Eli
My husband won't have sex with me.
我丈夫不愿跟我做爱
I just need to make sure it's not... Me.
我只是想确定这不是... 我的问题
It's not you.
不是的问题
Are you sure?
你确定?
Trust me. I used to work in construction.
相信我 我曾经在建筑业工作
My buddies would've gone crazy for you...
我的兄弟们会为你疯狂的...
Catcalls, uh, nasty gestures.
吹口哨 挑逗你
"Hey, you, with the sweater meats!
"嘿  你 火辣身材的那位!
If you ever need any work done, call me!"
如果你有什么需要 叫我哟!"
'Cause I got the perfect tool for the job!"
因为我有干那事的绝密武器!"
Y-you get the drift.
你很有资本
Yeah. I do.
是啊 我有
That was insulting and demeaning.
那相当的无礼 下流
Oh.
哦
Thank you so much.
太谢谢你了
Miss Britt?
Britt小姐?
The door was wide open.
门是开着的哦
- I got the paint. You want to check the color?
- 油漆拿来了 你想看看色么?
Eh.
呃
Is everything okay?
你还好吧?
Things are great.
还好
You want some wine?
你想喝酒么?
We're celebrating.
我们来庆祝
What's the occasion?
庆祝什么?
I am no longer married to a gay guy.
我再不和同志结婚了
Umberto was gay?
Umberto是个同志?
So you wasted your time
所以说你在厕所安那灯
Installing that light in the closet,
完全是在浪费时间
Because... He went flying out of there.
因为... 他就是从那儿跑的
At least you know now it wasn't you.
至少你知道一直都不是你的问题
Wasn't it?
不是吗?
He said that being married to me
他说跟我结婚
Was what convinced him that he liked men.
坚定了他喜欢男人这一想法
Oh. You could imagine what a boost to the ego that was.
哦 你可以想象这对人的自尊心是多么大的打击
Come on.
振作起来
You had a gay guy sleeping with you for two years,
你跟一个同志生活了两年
And those guys are pretty hard to land.
而那种男人是很难安定的
No. No, trust me.
不 不 相信我
No need to be sad.
没必要难过
You're a knockout.
你是绝代佳人
No, I-I-I need this hand back.
不 我... 我需要把这只手抽回来
It's hard to be a handyman without a-a hand.
对一个杂务工来说 少一只手会很麻烦
Mm.
嗯
Miss Britt, what are you doing?
Britt小姐 你在干嘛?
You put the mirror over my bed.
你真是让我如梦初醒啊
You know exactly what I'm doing.
你很清楚我要干什么
Are you sure about this? I don't want to take advantage of you.
你确定要这么做吗? 我不想趁人之危
Oh, I'm sure you'll be gentle.
哦 我知道你会很绅士的
Anyway,
不管怎样
I guess they're burying him on Saturday.
我猜他们会在礼拜六将他下葬
Obviously, you want to go.
很显然 你想去
Yeah.
是啊
I do.
确实
Oh, leave that black dress out.
哦 把这黑色礼服留在外面
I'll get it dry-cleaned for the funeral.
我拿去干洗 葬礼的时候穿
A little sexy for a funeral, isn't it?
在葬礼上 会不会太过性感?
Oh, I don't think Eli would mind.
哦 Eli不会介意的
Mom?
妈妈?
That's Penny. I'll be right back.
是Penny在叫 我一会就回来
Mom!
妈妈!
Hey, sweetie.
嘿 宝贝
What's up?
怎么了?
You said you would help me with my math.
你说过你会教我数学的
We're dividing fractions.
我们都学到分式整除了
Oh. I wish you'd caught me two chardonnays ago.
哦 你要是早在我喝下那两杯酒之前叫我就好了
Mom, you promised.
妈妈 你答应过我的
I know, but mommy's still planning Eli's memorial.
我知道 但是妈妈还得安排Eli的追悼会啊
Start without me.
别等我 自己先学吧
I'll be there in a little while.
我一会儿就过来
Oh, my gosh. Lynette, are you okay?
哦 天啊 Lynette 你还好吧?
The doctor just called. I'm pregnant.
医生刚打电话来 我怀孕了
This is fantastic!
太好了!
You...
你...
Yeah. Whoop-dee-doo.
是啊 很好
Honey, you don't sound too happy about this.
亲爱的 听起来你似乎不是太高兴
I was planning to go back to work.
我一直都想着重返工作
What? What a... what are you talking about?
什么? 你... 你在说什么?
I had it in the back of my mind for a while,
我已经有这个想法好久了
- And then yesterday, I got a ph...
- 就昨天 我接到一个电...
Hold it.
等等
Sorry. I was having trouble paying attention.
抱歉 刚才我有点无法集中精神
Jeffrey Cuevas is retiring in September.
Jeffrey Cuevas将在九月退休
I am the perfect person to step into his job,
而我是接手他位子的最佳人选
And that is exactly when Parker starts kindergarten.
而且那个时候Parker又正好上幼儿园了
The timing is like a dream.
这正是我梦寐以求的时机啊
But what about our dream of having a... a little girl?
我们不也一直梦寐以求吗 想要一个... 一个女儿?
This could be our chance.
这次是我们的机会啊
Oh, please. You know it's gonna be a boy. It's always a boy.
哦 拜托 你知道的这会是个儿子 我们一直都生儿子
It's just gonna pee in my face
他们就只会对着我的脸撒尿
And hide dead things in my shoes.
还偷偷地在我鞋子里放些该死的东西
I am doing this, Tom.
我要回去工作 Tom
I am going after this job.
我要接手这份工作
But who's gonna take care of the kids?
那谁来照顾我们的孩子呢?
Well, I was hoping you could cut back on your hours at work.
噢 我希望你能够减少你的工作时间
I can't do that.
我不能这么做
I have a career.
我有自己的事业
You did not just say that.
你不是就说说的吧
No, I... I didn't. I didn't.
不... 我... 我没 我什么也没说
Tom, I cannot just stay at home wiping noses.
Tom 我不能再呆家里给孩子擦鼻涕了
I need it for my sanity,
我要保持精力
And I need you to back me up.
我需要你支持我
Oh!
哦!
Mom?
妈妈?
Well, the kids are up.
瞧 孩子们起床了
They're gonna want their breakfast.
他们要吃早餐呢
And I'm gonna back you up by, uh, making it for 'em.
我去支持你 呃 去给他们做早餐
My hero.
真是我的英雄
Jeff Cuevas is fantastic,
Jeff Cuevas是很不错
But I know I could take his department to a whole new level.
但我清楚我能把他的部门提高一个等次
What the hell is that?
这该死的到底是什么?
Oh, my water broke.
哦 我的羊水破了
Take the overnight bag out to the car.
去把旅行袋拿到车上
Oh, three weeks.
哦 三个星期
That's a little soon, but, uh, sure, I could make that work.
有点太快了 不过 呃 没问题 我能接手那活儿
- For god sakes, Lynette, we gotta go to the hospital.
- 上帝啊 Lynette 我们得去医院了
In a minute. I'm trying to lock this job down.
就一分钟 我要就快把这工作搞定了
What kind of perks are we talking about here?
我们现在说的津贴是哪种?
Okay, you're having contractions. That's it. You...
拜托 你的子宫都开始收缩了 快生了  你...
I swear, if you touch this phone,
我发誓 如果你敢碰这电话
I will have this baby right here and then beat you with it!
我会在这里生小孩 然后用他来揍你
You're insane. We have to go.
你疯了 我们得去医院了
Could you hold on one second?
你能等一会儿吗?
We agreed I could go back to work
我们都谈妥我可以回去工作了
- After I gave birth.
- 在我生完孩子后
After, Lynette, not during!
是生完 Lynette 不在是生的时候!
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Is there any way we could finish this conversation tomorrow?
我们是不是能明天再谈?
Oh!
哦!
L... later in the day works better for me, too.
当... 当天晚点我也没关系的
Well, thank you very much.
好 太感谢你了
Bye. Hey. Whew! I got the job
再见 嘿 哇! 我得到这份工作了
Congratulations. The baby's arm is sticking out.
恭喜了 孩子的手都从你肚子伸出来了
Why don't you high-five it?
你想跟他拍掌欢呼一下吗?
Tom, I am in pain. Do you mind?
Tom 我快要痛死了 可以帮我吗?
Oh.
哦
You'll see, Tom.
你会明白的 Tom
I know. People say that you... Ooh!
我了解 人们常说... 哦!
You can't have it all, but I know we can.
鱼与熊掌不能兼得 但我知道我们可以
Oh, Mr. Swenson, I can't tell you how excited I am.
哦 Swenson夫人 我高兴得无法形容了
Maybe you could schedule a staff meeting
也许你可以安排一个职员会议
So I could hit the ground running on Monday.
之样我星期一就能走马上任了
No, no.
不 不好
No, it can't be Friday,
不 星期五不行
Because, remember, we agreed that we would start next week?
因为 你还记得吗 我们说好我可以下个星期才工作?
So again, thank you so much for this opportunity.
所以 再次感谢你给我这个机会
- Mrs. Scavo?
- Scavo太太?
Yeah?
嗯?
I think you might have forgotten somethin'.
我想你可能忘了些什么
Could you hold on a second?
你能等会吗?
Oh, my God.
哦 天啊
She's fine.
她很好
I was... I was on the phone.
我刚才... 我刚才在讲电话
- I was talking to my new boss, and I...
- 我正跟我的新老板谈话 我..
She was only in there for a minute.
她只在外面呆了一分钟
But it's 85 degrees outside. I've never done this before.
但是外面是85华氏度(属于高温) 我以前不会这样的
You got a lot on your mind... three kids and a newborn,
你有很多事情要处理... 三个孩子和一个新生儿
It sounds like a new job.
而且似乎还有一份新工作
Yeah, I do.
是的 是的
Yeah. It's a lot to handle.
对 有很多要处理呢
There you go.
来 给你
Mm.
嗯
I should probably get back to Susan's windows.
我现在要回去修Susan的窗户了
Uh, you take care.
呃 你好好照顾吧
Lynette, are you still there?
Lynette 还在吗?
Lynette?
Hello?
喂?
Are you still there?
你还在吗?
Hey. You coming back in?
嘿 你要过来吗?
No.
不了
I'm gonna go help my daughter with her homework.
我要去教我女儿做功课
Hey, Penny! Wait up!
嘿 Penny! 等等我!
Yard sale!
院庭旧货出售!
Oh! Good. You're here.
哦! 太好了 你在这儿
How are you, Eli?
你过得怎样 Eli?
Fine. You?
不错 你呢?
Great. Yeah, I haven't worn these jeans in a while,
很好 瞧 这条牛仔裤我好久没穿过了
And I found 20 bucks in the pocket.
我还在这口袋里找到20美元
Don't you just love when that happens?
有这样的美事感觉很好吧?
Also, Karl left me for his secretary,
还有 Karl因为他秘书抛弃了我
So I need you to change these locks.
所以我要你把这些锁都给换了
Oh, I'm so sorry.
哦 我抱歉
Oh, thanks, but don't be. Just hurry.
哦 谢谢 不过不需要 你抓紧点吧
Karl said he was coming by to get some of his stuff,
Karl说他要过来拿回他的东西
And I want this place to be a fortress by then.
我要他过来的时候进不了家门
You're doing all right, though?
你还好吧?
Oh, well, on one hand,
哦 是的 一方面
I got dumped for a pair of headlights named Brandy.
我因为一个叫做Brady的瘦削女人而被抛弃了
On the other, I reported Karl's credit cards stolen,
另一外面 我给Karl的信用卡报失挂停了
And I cut the pockets out of all of his pants.
我还把他的裤兜都剪烂了
So a little from column "a", a little from column "b".
所以你敬我一尺 我敬你一丈
Oh. Sorry.
哦 抱歉
Well, if it's any consolation, redheads are nuts.
哦 值得安慰的是 红头发的是魔鬼(西方传说)
What do you mean?
你这话是什么意思?
That she'll make his life a living hell.
她会使得他如同生活地炼狱
It sounds like what he deserves.
这听起来他罪有应得
Brandy's not a redhead. She's blonde.
Brandy不是红头发的 她是黄头发的
So, uh, you maybe want to go with a dead bolt this time?
那么 呃 你现在想把门给锁死吗?
What... Do... You... Know?
你都... 知道些... 什么?
I saw him around town a couple times with a redhead.
我有两次看到过他带着一个红头发的女人回来
Uh, people in the neighborhood were talking.
呃 周围的人都在谈论呢
I... I thought you knew.
我... 我以为你知道
I didn't.
我不知道
Would you feel any better
那你现在好受点了吗
Knowing that, uh, she's kinda chubby?
因为知道 呃 其实是个丰满的女人?
Just leave!
给我出去!
But what... but what about the locks?
那这些... 这些锁怎么办?
I... if Karl's coming...
我... 如果Karl过来...
Change the locks, then leave.
换好锁 然后出去
Okay, but I really am sorry...
好的 我真的很抱歉...
Change the locks, don't talk to me, then leave.
换好锁 不要跟我说话 然后出去
Susan?
Susan, did you call me?
Susan 是你给我打电话吗?
I couldn't really understand the message.
我听不懂你的口信是什么意思
Oh, wow.
哦 天啊
You want me to come back later?
你要我一会儿再来吗?
Are you all right?
你还好吧?
No. Of course you're not.
是啊 你当然不好过了
I heard you and Mike are getting divorced.
我听说你跟Mike离婚了
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
Probably not what you want to hear,
或许你不想听到这个
But I thought you were a great couple.
但我以前觉得你们是很好的一对
Thanks.
谢谢
Sweet.
真贴心
Do you... maybe you remember what you wanted me to do?
你... 或许你还记得你曾过叫我干什么吗?
Locks.
换锁
Change the locks. Got it.
换锁 明白了
Let me go see what I got out in the truck.
让我看看 我车上有什么工具
Susan...
I don't know much about love.
我不太了解爱是什么
I... I dabbled in it once or twice,
我曾经... 爱过一两次吧
But it always seemed more trouble than it was worth.
但似乎它招来的烦恼远多于回报
I told myself I wasn't missing much.
我安慰自己 我没有错过什么
But watching you all these years,
但这些年来 看着你
how... how hard you've tried, how...
你... 一直努力着...
how hurt you've been,
不论受到多大伤害
but you still...
你仍然...
keep getting back up, you dust yourself off,
努力着 重新振作
then you try again.
又一次投入其中
Maybe I am...
或许我...
missing something.
确实错过了很多
Maybe...
或许...
maybe it is worth it.
这一切都是值得的
And, um, I'm sure it's not gonna help
呃 我知道听我说这些
for you to hear me tell you this,
并不能带给你多大的帮助
but you're damn heroic to me.
但在我看来 你很伟大
You are.
是真的
Yeah.
好了
Hey. Just dropping these off. I finally got 'em cut.
嗨 我是来给你这个 终于配好了
Tell Jackson I'm sorry it took me so long.
花了这么长时间 替我向Jackson道声歉
Actually, um...
事实上 呃...
Jackson and I split up.
我和Jackson分手了
Wow. I'm sorry.
噢 我很抱歉
Am I sorry?
需要我这么说吗?
Oh, yeah.
噢 也许吧
He's a great guy.
他很好
I just, uh,
只是我 呃
want to be alone right now.
现在想一个人过
Well, good for you.
噢 这很好
Oh, hey. Mm?
噢 嘿 呃?
As long as you're here,
既然你来了
I think there's a loose shingle on my roof.
我的房顶上有块木瓦松脱了
Do you think maybe you could fix it for me?
你能帮我修理下吗?
Oh, I'd be happy to.
噢 我很乐意
But just so you know,
只是 你要知道
It'll be the last thing I ever fix for you. I'm retiring.
这是我最后一次帮你修理东西了 我要退休了
What?
什么?
Today's my last day.
今天是我最后一天工作了
You can't retire. I break too many things.
你不能退休... 我经常弄坏东西
I know. You paid for the trip to Hawaii I'm gonna take.
我知道 我去夏威夷的钱都是从你那赚来的
No, it's the right move. Be happy for me.
可不行 我得退休了 替我高兴吧
Hey, I am happy for you.
喂 我的确为你高兴
It's just, uh...
只是 呃...
This is gonna sound crazy.
听起来也许有点不可思议
What?
什么?
Um, I think you have been
呃 我一直把你视为
the most consistent male relationship in my life.
在我生命中最为牢靠的男性朋友
You're so stable and reliable, and I just...
你是这么的稳重可靠 我...
always thought you'd be around.
总是以为你会一直在我身边
Which is funny, because I don't really know anything about you.
最可笑的是 我几乎对你一无所知
Well, how about this... I fix your shingle,
那么 要不这样... 我帮你修理屋瓦
and when I'm done, you can ask me anything you want.
修好之后 随你想问什么都行
Great.
太棒了
I will go to the store right now and get some wine
我现在就去商店买些酒回来
so we can toast your retirement.
好为你的退休庆祝一下
I like that. Perfect way to end my time on Wisteria Lane.
我喜欢 给我的紫藤街生活一个完美谢幕
Ok.
好
What kind do you like... red or white?
你要哪种的... 红酒还是白酒?
Either one. Just make sure it's a screw top.
随便 只要没有开过的就行
Eli Scraggs was buried on Saturday,
Eli Scraggs的葬礼是在周六
and all the people that Eli had helped over the years
这些年里 所有曾被Eli帮助过的人
came to pay their last respects.
都去送上他们最后的敬意
But one person was missing.
除了一个人...
Someone who had changed Eli's life
那个人 用他永远无法忘怀的方式
in a way he never forgot.
改变了Eli的一生
Excuse me, ma'am,
不好意思 夫人
hope I'm not interrupting your day.
希望我没有打扰到你
Not at all. Can I help you?
没关系 有什么事可以帮你的吗?
I was hoping I could help you. I'm a handyman.
那正是我想要问的 我是一个杂务工
Just moved into town. Looking for work.
我刚搬进这里 想找份工作
Sorry. I, um, I don't have anything that needs fixing.
不好意思 我 呃 我这没有需要维修的东西
Well, if you ever do, uh, here's my card.
好吧 如果你有需要的话 呃 这是我的名片
Eli Scruggs
What a distinctive name.
很特别的名字呢
People do seem to remember it.
似乎大家都记得住
So if any of your friends, uh, need help,
那么 如果你的朋友需要帮忙的话
- I can do pretty much anything.
- 很多方面我都能帮上忙的
I don't know. Um...
我不知道 呃...
If you have a extra card or two, I... I could hand them out.
你能再给我几张名片吗 我好给她们
Oh, I'd really appreciate that.
噢 十分感谢
Oh. Oh.
噢 哦
Anyway...
无论如何...
Thank you for your time.
谢谢你 打扰了
I have a broken vase.
我有个坏了的花瓶
I'm sorry?
你说什么?
I... I was, uh, dusting the other day
我... 有一天 我打扫卫生时
and knocked it off the bureau, like an idiot.
不小心 像笨蛋一样让它从桌子上摔下来了
Anyway, I saved the pieces.
还好 我把碎片都留下来了
If you could glue it back together for me,
如果你能把它们粘回去
I'd really appreciate it.
我会十分感谢的
Oh, ma'am, you don't have to do that.
噢 太太 你用不着那样做的
Mr Scruggs,
Scruggs先生
I need my vase fixed.
我希望我的花瓶能修好
It means a lot to me.
它对我意义重大
Now you're not gonna make me beg, are you?
你总不会让我求你吧?
No, ma'am, I'm not.
不会 太太 不用
Good.
太好了
Come on in.
进来吧
Mrs Young?
Young太太?
Oh. Didn't mean to disturb you.
噢 我没想打扰你
Your front door was wide open.
你的前门大开着
Oh.
噢
Eli, I... I don't have any work for you today.
Eli 我... 我今天没有什么需要你帮忙的
I'm just here to drop off that handle you wanted.
我只是过来给你这个门把手
Finally found one that matched. Want me to install it?
好不容易找到适用的 需要我现在帮你装上吗?
Not today.
今天不用
Okay.
好的
I'll just be going then.
那我先走了
Eli, wait.
Eli 等等
What?
什么?
Do you remember this?
你还记得这个吗?
- Oh, right.
- 哦 是的
This is the very first thing you ever fixed for me.
这是你帮我修理的第一件东西
- Yeah, that must have been what, uh, two years ago?
- 是的 那都是 呃 两年前的事了?
Yeah.
是啊
- Is that glue really held, huh?
- 那个胶水还真好用呢?
Yeah.
是啊
I want you to have it.
我想把它送你
What?
什么?
Why?
为什么?
I've just been doing some thinking
我正在想着
about the people I know,
那些我认识的人
the ones who've walked into my life
那些走进我的生活
and made it better than it was before...
使之更为美好的人...
people like you.
像你一样
Anyway, I've... I've... I've never said "thank you."
总而言之 我... 我... 我从未对你说过一句"谢谢"
Oh, no, I'm... I'm the one who should thank you.
噢 不 我... 我才要对你说谢谢
You... you introduced me to all your friends.
是你... 是你把我介绍给你的朋友们
My business couldn't be better.
我的工作才开始有起色的
I'm so glad.
我很荣幸
Anyway, I, uh, I want you to have this.
无论如何 我想要你拿着这个
Mrs Young.
Young太太
Are you all right?
你还好吧?
Everything's fine.
一切都很好
Are you sure?
真的?
You should go now.
你该走了
So I look in the window,
然后我看进窗户
and there's blood everywhere...
里面到处都是血...
all over the walls and the ceiling...
整个墙面 天花板都是...
Not to mention, her hardwood floors,
更不用说她家的实木地板
which she just had installed last week.
她上个礼拜才装好的
I don't know what she was thinking.
我不明白她到底是在想什么
I just wish there had been some warning,
真希望有什么先兆
some sign that she would do such a thing.
暗示她会这么做
Eli Scruggs sat in his truck for almost an hour,
Eli Scruggs在车里坐了将近一个小时
devastated that he had done nothing to save me.
为他什么也没做 没能拯救我而感到难过
He then made a quiet vow to god...
那时 他暗自向上帝许下誓言...
from that moment forward,
从那一刻起
he would do what he could to help people,
他将尽其所能去帮助他人
to help them fix their lives.
帮助他们修复自己的生活
And for the rest of his life,
而他在之后的人生
that's exactly what he did.
所做的正如他曾许愿的那样
That was a lovely service.
这个做的不错
Eli would've liked it.
Eli一定会喜欢的
- Hell of a turnout.
- 世事难料
Who knew he had so many friends?
谁料到他会有这么多的朋友呢?
I'm not surprised. He was a good man.
这并不奇怪 他是个好人
I can't help feeling
我止不住的想
there's more we could have done to honor him.
我们能做得更多 用以悼念他
Well, let's just make sure we remember him.
噢 我们只要确保永远记住他就行了
Eli would have said that's more than most people get.
Eli会说这将比大多数人得到的还要多
And he would have been right...
那他说的一定会是对的...
As usual.
一如既往
Wait.
等等
I wanted to fix something for Eli for a change.
我想转换角色 也帮Eli修一次东西
And somewhere,
在某处
in a place reserved for the very best of us,
一个聚集着最美好的灵魂的地方
Eli Scruggs smiled and said, "thank you."
Eli Scruggs微笑着说了句"谢谢"